(843) 822-9802

HUNT.KELSEARYAN@GMAIL.COM

www.linkedin.com/in/k-ryanhunt

https://github.com/k-ryanhunt

KELSEA HUNT UX/UI DESIGNER

SUMMARY

Quick-learning web designer with a passion for all things design. Contracted to design logos for companies. Recognized multiple times for outstanding job performance by Regional Presidents of Wells Fargo. Able to effectively communicate with other team members to increase productivity and efficiency of the work day. Full Stack Web Development certificate earned through University of Denver. 2-3 years of experience in freelance designing and creation.

SKILLS

```
HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | jQuery | Node.JS | PHP | Express.JS | React.JS | MongoDB | MySQL | MVC |
```

PROJECTS

- Concert Finder Implemented front end and back end to create a website that pulled information from a public API
 - HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript
 - https://github.com/k-rvanhunt/Project-One-Concert-Finder
 - https://k-ryanhunt.github.io/Project-One-Concert-Finder/
- Tripr implemented a database, validation, front end, and back end to create a website that stores your trips under a created profile
 - HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Handlebars | Shell
 - o https://github.com/k-ryanhunt/Project-2-Travel-Green
 - o https://tripr-project2.herokuapp.com/

EXPERIENCE

Wells Fargo, Parker - Personal Banker

MAY 2017 - JUNE 2021

- Built strong relationships with clients through follow up conversations, asked questions to understand their needs, and understand their financial situation
- Commissioned to educate and train new team members
- Built relationships with company partners and matched them with client needs
- Opened new consumer and business accounts, completed account maintenance, submitted credit applications
- Educated customers on digital resources and tools available to them
- Complied with policy and procedure to manage risk to our customers and company

Benefitfocus, Daniel Island — Benefits Administrator

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY 2017

- Company health report scored consistently 97% or higher based on performance and customer service
- Resolved phone inquiries that are technical and nontechnical in nature
- Consistently provided clients with the proper information to guide them toward an informed decision
- Accurately documented each phone call with descriptive details of each interaction in case-tracking software
- Provided exemplary customer service in each interaction

Lighthouse Tax Service Center, Ladson — Office Manager

AUGUST 2012 - MAY 2015

- Customized QuickBooks profiles to best accommodate the needs of each individual company
- Reconciled bank statements monthly to locate any discrepancies
- Managed finances and registers for 9 companies at a time
- Received and processed payroll for multiple clients on a weekly or bi-weekly basis
- Generated payroll, tax, and profit and loss reports for the client
- Created company forms and files to suit the company's needs as the client base continued to grow
- Maintained office efficiency by planning and implementing office systems and equipment

Phillips Van Heusen, North Charleston — Retail Manager

AUGUST 2006 - JANUARY 2011

- Delegated store's operations to a team of 4-6 employees
- Generated sales, profit and loss, and quarterly sales incentive reports
- Scheduled staff and prepared weekly payroll for maximum efficiency
- Properly process incoming shipments and fulfill outgoing mail orders
- Maintained office staff by recruiting and training employees

EDUCATION

University of Denver, Denver - UX/UI Web Design Certificate

FEBRUARY 2021 - JULY 2021, DENVER

Trident Technical College, Charleston - Graphic Design

SEPTEMBER 2007 - MAY 2009, CHARLESTON

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Customers at the Heart award
- Exceptional customer service email from the Atlantic Regional President for Wells Fargo

PROMOTIONS

- Lead Teller to Personal Banker (SAFE)
- Teller to Lead Teller
- Office Administrator to Office Manager
- Sales Associate to Assistant Manager